# Ojo Emmanuel Olusegun

House 10, Oke Street, Gbagada, Lagos

+234 708 932 7940, emmanuelojo1234@gmail.com

### **Executive Summary**

Possessing great research, analytical skills and experience in handling data. With the ability to assimilate, effectively communicate, and interpret data in a high-stress, fast-paced environment. An innovative thinker, who develops procedures to get the job done in quick succession and meet set goals.

### **Education History**

**2014 – 2018** University of Lagos, Akoka, Nigeria

Bachelor of Education in Mathematics Education

(Second Class Upper Honours)

**2011 – 2014** Odorgonno Senior High School, Accra, Ghana

Secondary School Certificate (WAEC & Nov/Dec)

## **Work Experience**

Jun 2019 – May 2020 Damtoy School, Ogombo, Lagos

Mathematics and Computer (National Youth Service Corps)

**Apr 2019 - Jun 2019 Debiruss Schools,** Ajah, Lagos

Intern, Mathematics Department

Nov 2017 – Feb 2018 Lagos City College, Sabo, Lagos

**Teaching Practice/ Intern, Mathematics and Physics Department** 

### **Skills**

**Programming** Python, SQL

**Visualization** Jupyter Notebook, Excel Charts, Tableau

**Database** MySQL

Web Development HTML, CSS, JavaScript

Soft Skills Excellent verbal and written communication skills,

presentation and negotiation skills, maintenance of work

ethics and integrity.

### **Volunteering**

• Web designing, Jahdai Farms, (May, 2020)

• Media and Online Team, Chapel of Christ our Light (CCOL), University of Lagos, (2017-2018)

Skills gained: creativity, written communication, presentation skills, teamwork, adhere to deadlines, self motivation, willing to learn

**Hobbies** Front-end web development, travelling and exploring new places

**<u>Referees</u>** Available on request